A once in a lifetime second chance.
Searching for David's Heart is a adventure, tv movie film directed by Paul Hoen.
After Her brother David is killed in a car accident, Darcy begins a journey to find the recipient of her brother's
heart in the hopes of finding a piece of her brother still alive as well as her own peace of mind.
Darcy Deeton, played by Danielle Panabaker.
Sam, played by Ricky Ullman.
Claire Deeton, Darcy's mother, played by Jayne Brook.
Winston, played by Kendre Berry.
Sexton, played by Don Brady.
Jock #1, played by Kyle Clements.
Searching for David's Heart is a 1998 young-adult novel by Cherie Bennett.
The author is a screenwriter, novelist, playwright, and columnist for
the San Diego Union-Tribune and other Copley newspapers.